<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sports &#8211; Space Casino News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/category/sports/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 22:07:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Manchester United transfer news: Dean Henderson, Mason Mount &#038; David De Gea latest</title>
		<link>https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/2023/06/06/manchester-united-transfer-news-dean-henderson-mason-mount-david-de-gea-latest/</link>
					<comments>https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/2023/06/06/manchester-united-transfer-news-dean-henderson-mason-mount-david-de-gea-latest/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 22:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/?p=63</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SAMUEL LUCKHURST DISSECTS OLE GUNNAR SOLSKJAER&#8217;S RECENT COMMENTS Dimitar Berbatov believes David de Gea deserves to continue as Manchester United&#8217;s number one goalkeeper but that Dean Henderson deserves a proper chance at...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SAMUEL LUCKHURST DISSECTS OLE GUNNAR SOLSKJAER&#8217;S RECENT COMMENTS<br />
Dimitar Berbatov believes David de Gea deserves to continue as Manchester United&#8217;s number one goalkeeper but that Dean Henderson deserves a proper chance at Old Trafford to show what he can do.</p>
<p>De Gea has been first choice at United for much of his career at Old Trafford, since joining from Atletico Madrid in the summer of 2011 as Edwin van der Sar&#8217;s replacement. The 32-year-old has made approaching 550 appearances for United in more than a decade.</p>
<p>In that time, he has won the Premier League, FA Cup, League Cup twice and the Europa League too. However, his contract with United is poised to expire this summer and he is yet to sign the fresh terms offered.</p>
<p>READ MORE: Man United&#8217;s remaining Premier League fixtures compared with Newcastle, Liverpool FC and rivals</p>
<p>United are happy to give De Gea a new contract providing he signs on reduced terms. The goalkeeper is in negotiations over an extension and the official announcement is expected soon.</p>
<p>Dean Henderson has spent the season in the Premier League on loan at Nottingham Forest. He will return to Old Trafford this summer after not playing since mid-January for Forest following a torn thigh, which he has had successful surgery on and is poised to be ready for action in time for pre-season.</p>
<p>Berbatov believes de Gea deserves to continue as United&#8217;s number one shot-stopper, but that Henderson also deserves to have a chance at Old Trafford which the former striker feels the 26-year-old has not had yet. He believes a fight for the number one spot is something which would benefit both de Gea and Henderson, but that Mike Maignan of AC Milan is a player which Erik ten Hag ought to consider if he wants to bring in reinforcements this summer.</p>
<p>Speaking to Betfred, Berbatov said: “If somebody that’s better than David de Gea comes along, challenges him for his place and proves themselves to be better than David, then of course that somebody needs a chance to be the club’s number one.</p>
<p>“At the moment, I believe that De Gea should be Manchester United’s number one. David is making mistakes and he will make mistakes in the future, but you can’t forget the many times that he’s saved the club from defeat. He deserves more credit than he gets. He’s done an awful lot for Manchester United and he’s a true great.</p>
<p>“I saw that Erik ten Hag said that he counts on David to stay at the club and it’s obvious that David needs to work on his footwork, as well as his ability to play out from the back, and I’m sure that he’s aware of this. Those are the only things that I believe he needs to work on.</p>
<p>“I believe that Dean Henderson deserves a chance at Manchester United, as I don’t believe he’s been given a chance previously. He needs to be given a real chance to show what he can do. If Erik ten Hag gives him a chance to prove himself next season, then I believe that will be beneficial for both Dean and David de Gea, as David needs to be properly challenged.</p>
<p>“If the club decides to go into the transfer market for a new goalkeeper this summer instead, then Mike Maignan of AC Milan is very good in my opinion and he deserves to be looked at by Manchester United.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/2023/06/06/manchester-united-transfer-news-dean-henderson-mason-mount-david-de-gea-latest/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bikash is giving a chance to go to Argentina and watch Messi play</title>
		<link>https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/2023/06/06/bikash-is-giving-a-chance-to-go-to-argentina-and-watch-messi-play/</link>
					<comments>https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/2023/06/06/bikash-is-giving-a-chance-to-go-to-argentina-and-watch-messi-play/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 22:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/?p=60</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bikash, Bangladesh&#8217;s largest mobile financial service provider, announced a brand partnership with Argentina Football Association (AFA) on May 8 . They are the first and only Bangladeshi company to be the brand...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bikash, Bangladesh&#8217;s largest mobile financial service provider, announced a brand partnership with Argentina Football Association (AFA) on May 8 . They are the first and only Bangladeshi company to be the brand partner of the World Cup winning Argentina team.</p>
<p>Bikash then announced that they will take initiatives to increase the contact of Bangladeshi fans with Argentine football stars. As part of that initiative, Bikash&#8217;s new campaign is being launched, during which shopping at Bikash will give you a chance to visit Argentina to watch the Lionel Messi-Emiliano Martinez-Julian Alvarez match.</p>
<p>A source in the development said that the campaign, which will start from June 8, will continue till June 28. 7 people who spend the most every week using Bikash &#8216;Payment&#8217; will get a total of 21 people in three weeks to go to Argentina and watch the game of Argentina national team.</p>
<p>In this campaign, Bikash will pay the air tickets, hotel accommodation expenses of the winners. According to the FIFA international schedule, the tour will be arranged when the Argentina team plays at home next time. The winners of the campaign will be contacted by BKash and informed about the detailed itinerary including match date, opponent, venue.</p>
<p>During the World Cup in Qatar last year, the intense love of the people of Bangladesh for the Argentina football team became the news of the global media . The strong emotions of the people of this country about Lionel Messi also touched the people of Argentina. Following this, the diplomatic relations of the two countries got a new dimension, then last month AFA&#8217;s brand partnership with Bikash.</p>
<p>Bikash and AFA expressed hope that this partnership would allow Bangladeshi football fans to get closer to their favorite stars in the Argentina team, increase the exchange of love and strengthen the football relationship between the two countries. Bikash&#8217;s new campaign is the first step in that series of initiatives.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/2023/06/06/bikash-is-giving-a-chance-to-go-to-argentina-and-watch-messi-play/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
