<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Health &#8211; Space Casino News</title>
	<atom:link href="https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/category/health/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 22:02:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Benefits of sex: 5 things that make sex a good workout</title>
		<link>https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/2023/06/06/benefits-of-sex-5-things-that-make-sex-a-good-workout/</link>
					<comments>https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/2023/06/06/benefits-of-sex-5-things-that-make-sex-a-good-workout/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 22:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/?p=53</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a landmark move, Sweden became the first country to recognize sex as a sport. So why is sex a good workout? Read on for his 5 benefits of fitness through sex....]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a landmark move, Sweden became the first country to recognize sex as a sport. So why is sex a good workout? Read on for his 5 benefits of fitness through sex.</p>
<p>Exercise is essential to maintaining a healthy lifestyle. From hitting the gym to participating in outdoor activities, we actively seek out ways to keep our bodies healthy and active. Surprisingly, one of his fun activities that is often overlooked as a potential workout is sex. Ladies, the benefits of sex aren’t just physical pleasures, they can also help improve her level of fitness.</p>
<p>While going to the gym and working out at home are irreplaceable, Healthshot is working with Shobha Subramanian, a physician consultant at Fortis Hospital Mulund, Mumbai, to understand why sex is good physical activity. We spoke with Dr. Itrikar.</p>
<p>Here’s why sex can be a good workout<br />
When you think about sex, you also have to think about stamina and flexibility. Indulging in sex often helps. Here are five reasons why sex can be a good workout, according to Dr. Subramanian.</p>
<p>1. Sex Increases Your Heart Rate<br />
As with any aerobic or aerobic exercise, your heart rate may increase during sex. Increased heart rate strengthens the heart muscle and helps promote cardiovascular health. In addition, increased blood flow improves oxygen supply to different parts of the body and strengthens the immune system.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Having sex improves heart health. Image credit: Freepik<br />
2. Burn calories<br />
Sex is a calorie-burning activity. That’s why intercourse helps burn calories and contributes to weight management. However, the exact number of calories burned depends on factors such as time, intensity, and body weight. A small study of 21 healthy heterosexual couples in their 20s, published in the Public Science Library journal PLOS One, found that during a 24-minute sex session (including foreplay), men averaged It showed that 101 calories (4.2 calories per person) were consumed. 1 minute), women burned 69 calories (3.1 calories per minute). Although the number of calories burned is small, it indicates that this intimate activity may contribute to overall calorie expenditure.</p>
<p>3. Muscle work<br />
During sex, different muscles in the body work together. Depending on the position and movement involved, you can train your core, legs, buttocks and even your upper body muscles. Regular sex helps tone and strengthen these muscle groups.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Also read: How to use lube for better, smoother sex</p>
<p>4. Reduce stress and improve mood<br />
There is no doubt that sex helps release endorphins, the body’s natural feel-good hormones. They calm the mind and lighten the spirit, providing an immediate mood boost. The best time to have sex is first thing in the morning. Morning sex can leave anyone feeling more relaxed, focused, and upbeat throughout the day. Overall, sex is a way to relax and improve your overall health.</p>
<p>Having sex relieves stress. Image credit: Shutterstock<br />
5. Improved flexibility and balance<br />
Certain sex positions often require flexibility and a wide range of motion. Practicing different sex positions improves range of motion, flexibility and stability. Additionally, it helps to stretch and relax your muscles. Therefore, regular sexual activity can improve overall physical performance.</p>
<p>Note that while sex has these benefits, it should not be considered a substitute for a regular exercise routine. Incorporating other forms of physical activity, such as cardio and strength training, remains important for maintaining overall fitness and health. Apart from this, please prioritize open communication and the use of appropriate safeguards to ensure a safe and positive experience.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/2023/06/06/benefits-of-sex-5-things-that-make-sex-a-good-workout/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Global Smart Wearables Market Evaluation, By Product, By Sector</title>
		<link>https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/2023/06/06/global-smart-wearables-market-evaluation-by-product-by-sector/</link>
					<comments>https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/2023/06/06/global-smart-wearables-market-evaluation-by-product-by-sector/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/?p=50</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEW YORK, June 6, 2023 (Globe Newswire) — Reportlinker.com presents “Global Smart Wearables Market Assessment, By Product, By Application, By Distribution Channel, By Region, Opportunity and Forecast, 2016-2030. ” announced the release...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK, June 6, 2023 (Globe Newswire) — Reportlinker.com presents “Global Smart Wearables Market Assessment, By Product, By Application, By Distribution Channel, By Region, Opportunity and Forecast, 2016-2030. ” announced the release of the report. – https://www.reportlinker.com/p06465608/?utm_source=GNW</p>
<p>Smart wearables have exploded in popularity around the world. From health trackers to smartwatches, these products help individuals stay connected in unimaginable ways. The global smart wearables market size is valued at USD 72.19 billion in 2022 and is expected to reach USD 231.82 billion in 2030, at a CAGR of 15.7% over the forecast period from 2023 to 2030. grow in The market is expected to maintain its current growth rate. Increased adoption of IoT and connected devices, increased awareness of health and fitness, and expansion of e-commerce platforms will lead to further growth in the years that follow. Moreover, increasing usage of smart wearables in the healthcare industry is boosting the market. Healthcare facilities are working to use wearable devices to check a patient’s vital signs and give advance warning if a problem arises. In addition, some wearables are intended to help people with chronic diseases cope with difficulties. These devices can track medication adherence and symptom intensity and provide personalized recommendations and assistance.</p>
<p>With the growing demand for wearable devices in the enterprise environment and increased investment in wearable technology start-ups, there is plenty of room for expansion. In addition, increasing use of wearable devices in virtual and augmented reality applications and increasing demand for fashion and luxury wearables have boosted the demand for smart wearables market on a global level. Additionally, the shift to remote work and online education has increased the demand for smart wearables that can not only detect physical activity but also offer features such as sleep tracking and stress monitoring.</p>
<p>Advanced sensors and features</p>
<p>Technological advances are driving the global market for smart wearables, electronic devices worn on the body that connect to the Internet and smartphones. With the growth of smartphones and the Internet of Things (IoT), wearables are becoming an increasingly popular way to collect data, monitor health, and connect with the environment. One of the key technological improvements driving the wearable business is the development of smaller and more powerful sensors and processors. These improvements have made it possible to build wearables that can measure a wide range of biometric data, including heart rate, blood pressure, and even brain waves. In addition, the development of new materials and manufacturing processes is also a key driver of the wearable market on a global level. These advances have enabled the development of wearables that are more comfortable, durable and fashionable than ever before.</p>
<p>Target dynamic demographics such as people with disabilities</p>
<p>Many companies target different demographics, such as child-centric, gender-specific, and disabled. For example, South Korean startup Dot Inc. is a company focused on developing smart wearables for visually impaired individuals. The company’s product, the Dot Watch, is a Braille smartwatch that uses Braille tactile cells to display notifications, messages, and time, making information self-accessible to people with visual impairments. The company received his US$500,000 grant from the South Korean government’s Tech Incubator Program for Startups (TIPS) and his US$100,000 grant from the ActnerLab accelerator. Therefore, market players in this industry are targeting different demographics to gain market share, thus enabling market expansion.</p>
<p>government efforts</p>
<p>Governments in many countries are promoting the use of smart wearables. As Japan’s healthcare spending rises, the government is adopting various methods to save costs by increasing R&amp;D investment and introducing regulations on digital health products and services. Recent trends indicate that Japanese customers are more interested in cutting-edge products from US digital health companies. The smartphone usage rate in Japan is 90.8% among those aged 13-19 and 99.0% among those aged 20-29. The majority of Japanese teens and young adults, including university students aged 18-22, use smartphones all day long. For this reason, the Japanese government has focused on implementing various strategies to boost demand for smart wearable products in the country.</p>
<p>Adoption of smartwatches and fitness bands increases</p>
<p>Growing consumer interest in fitness and wellness is one of the main drivers of the smart wearables industry. People are becoming more health conscious and want to know how to measure their physical activity to improve their overall health. Smart wearables are becoming increasingly popular because they can track exercise, monitor health, and quickly access information while on the move. These devices are not only stylish, they are also efficient with features like heart rate monitoring, sleep tracking and calorie tracking. Furthermore, the introduction of the latest technologies such as artificial intelligence and machine learning is accelerating the evolution of smart grids.</p>
<p>Smart apparel and clothing gaining popularity</p>
<p>Growing applications of smart clothing in various industries such as sports and fitness, healthcare, military, and defense are driving the global smart clothing market. Over the projected period, the growing need to monitor physical activity via sensors is likely to drive demand for smart clothing. According to a recent World Economic Forum (WEF) poll, 92.1% of business owners expect 10% of people to wear internet-connected clothing by 2025. In addition, newly created advanced fibers such as nanofibers and hybrid materials may be used. To promote the smart clothing industry in the coming years.</p>
<p>Impact of the novel coronavirus disease (COVID-19)</p>
<p>The global smart wearables market has been greatly impacted by the COVID-19 pandemic. In 2020, global market sales declined due to supply chain disruptions and retail store closures. However, the pandemic has underscored the importance of health monitoring, driving demand for smartwatches and fitness trackers that can measure vital metrics such as heart rate, oxygen saturation and body temperature. Remote patient monitoring is also growing in popularity, with healthcare workers deploying smart wearables to remotely monitor patients and reduce the chance of viral transmission.</p>
<p>Effects of the Russo-Ukrainian War</p>
<p>The Russo-Ukrainian war has disrupted supply chains at the global level. Many smart wearable devices are made in China, a major supplier of electronic components. But China is a close ally of Russia, and the war cut off supply lines for these parts. The result has been component shortages, smart wearable manufacturing delays, and price hikes. In addition, the war forced many manufacturers to relocate. This could be an opportunity for other countries to strengthen their manufacturing capacity and become more competitive in the global smart wearables market.</p>
<p>Status and prospects of major companies</p>
<p>The global smart wearables market is highly competitive, and market players are looking for a competitive edge in this rapidly growing industry, primarily by catering to the millennial demographic.</p>
<p>Leading companies in the industry employ various advertising strategies to effectively reach target audiences, increase brand awareness and drive product sales. Collaboration and influencer marketing are widely adopted by companies today. For example, Fitbit has partnered with fitness influencers and big-name artists such as Will His Smith and Jules Sebastian to promote their Fitness His trackers and smartwatches. Additionally, the company collaborates with TV shows, movies, and popular events to showcase its products. One example is his use of Fitbit devices in his TV series like “Brooklyn Nine-Nine.” It shows the character using his Fitbit products as part of his daily life.</p>
<p>Market Xcel reports answer the following questions:</p>
<p>• Is the current and future market size for the product/service in question global or country-specific?</p>
<p>• How is the market divided into different product/service segments and market size and growth for each segment?</p>
<p>• What are the market potentials of the various product segments and their investment cases?</p>
<p>• How is the market projected to develop in the future and what are the factors driving or inhibiting growth?</p>
<p>• What is the business environment and regulatory situation specific to your product/service?<br />
Read the full report: https://www.reportlinker.com/p06465608/?utm_source=GNW</p>
<p>About Report Linker<br />
ReportLinker is an award-winning market research solution. Reportlinker finds and organizes the latest industry data so you can instantly get all the market research you need in one place.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jumio.spacecasino.co.uk/2023/06/06/global-smart-wearables-market-evaluation-by-product-by-sector/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
